你在家吗
弟弟
新年快乐呀
弟弟嘿嘿
有没有想我
我怎么来了
你这话问的这不过年了吗
姐姐心想你一定是一个人
所以就来陪你啦
哎哟哭什么
这么想我吗
乖不哭啊
姐姐给你买了好多好多好吃的来吃吧
来姐姐摸摸你的头
乖孩子不要哭啦
嘿嘿真乖
来坐下吃东西
我为什么不吃
姐姐来之前就已经吃完了
而且这些都是给你买的
怎么样
我对你
你你干什么
好你个小家伙居然敢这样子
那么就别怪姐姐
我不客气了
不许躲哦
果然小孩子就是小孩子
把你按在沙发上
你就没力气反抗了呢
喜欢姐姐这样为你的方式吗
你怎么脸红不说话
那我继续咯
嘿嘿好久没有这样亲你了
回想上一次还是好几年前的事了
那个时候你还真就是个小孩子
很可爱的
怎么脸红什么
你都这么大了
还害羞吗
你都快和姐姐一边高了
那我为什么说小孩子就是小孩子呢
哼哼
因为你在姐姐眼里永远都是小孩子
为什么
因为我比你大
就这么简单
大的就是要笑着笑的
嘿嘿你就庆幸吧
有个这么好的姐姐
哼来弟弟上床
我说上床真乖
来让姐姐抱抱
什么你已经长大了
不能和我这么亲密
现在知道自己长大了
我管你呢
嘿嘿没力气了吧
怎么不喜欢姐姐抱着你吗
不喜欢也得给我喜欢
哎哟呼吸都变得急促了
好好好
姐姐松开一点
什么让我不要抱着你了
呵呵莫不就不
既然你被我抓到了
就不要再想着跑了
乖乖的让我抱抱
做我的充电宝
让我充充电
嗯真舒服啊
啊哭了吗
好好好哦
姐姐不欺负你了
好不容易陪弟弟过年
可不能一直这样欺负你啊
唉你说弟弟时间过得可真快呀
一转眼又是一年过去了
你都快有我高了
小的时候盼望你长大
现在反而不希望了
越怕你长大
姐姐就越老一岁
乖弟弟不许哭了
姐姐不会再走了
姐姐会永远陪着你
至少每周会和你一起住两天
你不要赶姐姐走哦
你也不希望姐姐一个人孤零零地睡在大街上吧
真乖好啦
跨完年就早点休息吧
不要因为这个把身体累垮了
要不然我会很心疼的
来嘛
弟弟让姐姐抱着你
哼哼很乖呢
你刚刚要是这样
就不会有那个事情发生了
好啦
早点休息吧
晚安
我的小弟弟
♪ I wanna say you love me ♪
♪ That's just can't live without me ♪
♪ Even if you have to lie ♪
♪ I just wanna hear you say ♪
♪ I wanna be the one ♪
♪ You dream of ♪
♪ But when your nose all your secrets ♪
♪ When you can't live without ♪
♪ Even if it hurts to stay to be the one to hold me down ♪
♪ Take me out and base the world side by side ♪
♪ Say you'll be ♪
♪ You'll be mine ♪
♪ You'll be my one day ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ When will i hear you calling my name ♪
♪ Cause you don't know what it's like on this side ♪
♪ Could it be ♪
♪ I will be wa with you ♪
♪ I wanna feel the touch your lips ♪
♪ The closeness of your body ♪
♪ Would you wanna be my first kiss one of me last ♪
♪ And only you're the one ♪
♪ I wanna go with share life ♪
♪ Middle of family ♪
♪ Don't you wanna be the one ♪
♪ The world at this happy ending ♪
♪ Be the one to hold me down ♪
♪ Take me out and face the world side by side say ♪
♪ You'll be ♪
♪ You'll be mine ♪
♪ You'll be my one day ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ When will i hear you calling my name ♪
♪ Cause you don't know what like on this side ♪
♪ Could it be ♪
♪ I still be be with you ♪
♪ Taste my hands ♪
♪ Leave me to the place ♪
♪ We can go out ♪
♪ Make me smile ♪
♪ Running more of your love ♪
♪ So that one day ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ I could hear you ♪
♪ Calling my name ♪
♪ Cause you ♪
♪ You don't know what it's like on this side ♪
♪ Could it be possibly be with you ♪
♪ Be with you ♪